[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what country did Charles Darwin experience an earthquake, leading him to form a theory on the movements of the Earths crust?", "correct_answer": "Chile", "incorrect_answers": ["Australia", "France", "South Africa"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the first jet fighter to hit Mach 3.2?", "correct_answer": "MIG 25 Foxbat", "incorrect_answers": ["Lockheed f-17-Eagle", "F-15 Falcon", "F-22 Raptor"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What Academy Award did the 1962 movie Days of Wine and Roses, directed by Blake Edwards, win in 1963?", "correct_answer": "Best Original Song", "incorrect_answers": ["Best Actress", "Best Art Direction", "Best Actor"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Generally, how many times in an interval of 5 hours do lions mate?", "correct_answer": "10", "incorrect_answers": ["1", "5", "20"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which fictional character stated, I dont mind flying, but what youre doing is suicide.?", "correct_answer": "Obi Wan Kenobi", "incorrect_answers": ["Anakin Skywalker", "Padme", "Mace Windu"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the flag on James Bond\u2019s parachute in the skiing scene in the movie The Spy Who Loved Me?", "correct_answer": "The Union Jack", "incorrect_answers": ["The US Flag", "The Skull And Bones Pirate Flag", "The United Nations Flag"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which country is the European Union\u2019s biggest lake located?", "correct_answer": "In Sweden", "incorrect_answers": ["In Finland", "In Poland", "In Hungary"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which river in China caused a flood of mammoth proportions in 1931?", "correct_answer": "Yellow", "incorrect_answers": ["Pearl", "Red", "Tumen"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the film Walk the Line, the part of Cashs long-time friend, Waylon Jennings was played by Jennings  son in real life. What is his name?", "correct_answer": "Shooter Jennings", "incorrect_answers": ["Harvey Jennings", "Hank Jennings", "Stormer Jennings"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is Rasputias dance teacher in the comedy Norbit?", "correct_answer": "Buster", "incorrect_answers": ["Charlie", "Billy", "Leroy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of Socks companion at the White House during the Clinton Administration?", "correct_answer": "Buddy", "incorrect_answers": ["Shoes", "Bailey", "Buster"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The name of cobras, which are very venomous, comes from the Portuguese cobra de capello. What does this mean?", "correct_answer": "Snake with hood", "incorrect_answers": ["Poisonous hat", "Poisonous nose", "Snake with nose"]}]